state-election.info 2014-12-20

# Presidential Election | Privacy Policy

## Privacy Policy

Your privacy is important to us and we provide this notice to explain our online policies and the manner in which your information is collected, used, communicated and disclosed.

Our website, as commonly practiced amongst most websites, does collect and use log files containing certain information about the visits to our website such as the number and frequency of visitors to individual pages. These statistics are used internally by our staff to improve upon and track the progress of the website. 

The information we collect is NOT linked to any personally identifiable information such as your name, email address, physical address, telephone number, social security numbers, bank account numbers or credit card numbers. We DO NOT collect information that would allow us to identify the particular visitors to our website.

We also use third party advertisements to support our site. Some of these advertisers may use technology such as cookies and web beacons which will also send these advertisers information including your IP address, your ISP, the browser you used to visit our site, and in some cases, whether you have Flash installed. This is generally used for geotargeting purposes or showing certain ads based on specific sites visited.

We may also use DART cookies for ad serving through Google’s DoubleClick, which places a cookie on your computer when you are browsing the web and visit a site using DoubleClick advertising. This cookie is used to serve ads specific to you and your interests and may be targeted based on your previous browsing history. DART uses “non personally identifiable information”. It does NOT track personal information about you, such as your name, email address, physical address, telephone number, social security numbers, bank account numbers or credit card numbers. You can opt-out of this ad serving on all sites using this advertising by visiting [http://www.doubleclick.com/privacy/dart_adserving.aspx](http://www.doubleclick.com/privacy/dart_adserving.aspx)

You can chose to disable or selectively turn off our cookies or third-party cookies in your browser settings, or by managing preferences in programs such as Norton Internet Security. However, this can affect how you are able to interact with our site as well as other websites. This could also include the inability to login to services or programs such as forums or accounts.

Deleting cookies does not mean you are permanently opted out of any advertising program. Unless you have settings that disallow cookies, the next time you visit a site running the advertisements, a new cookie will be added.

Under no circumstances would we divulge personal information about any individual user to any third party - because we don't have any!.

We are committed to conducting our website in accordance with these principles in order to ensure that the confidentiality of personal information is protected and maintained. This notice applies to all information collected from or submitted to these websites. We will only collect personal information by lawful and fair means and readily make available our policies and practices relating to the management of personal information. If you have any questions, concerns, or comments about our privacy policy please feel free to contact us.
